badindian.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy! Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to www.badindian.com will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to [let us know](mailto:admin@badindian.com).

### **Resale or disclosure of information to third parties:**

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.  
Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

### **Browser information collected on the website:**

badindian.com analyzes website logs to constantly improve the value of the materials available on our website. Our website logs **are not personally identifiable** , and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site.

### **Use of cookies:**

We do not use cookies on this site. However since we use outside companies to display ads on our site, these ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

### ** External Links:**

This site contains links to other sites. **badindian.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

### Advertisements

www.badindian.com works with third parties, that serve ads to this site. Their individual privacy statement can be seen at their respective sites. [www.badindian.com](http://www.badindian.com/) as no control over data collected by these sites.
